jaycut.com 2011-06-05

# Privacy Policy | JayCut

**Privacy Policy**

  Updated March 1, 2010

  JayCut is committed to safeguarding the privacy of visitors to this website and users of our products and services; this policy sets out how JayCut will treat your personal information. This Privacy Policy supplements the JayCut [Terms of Use](http://jaycut.com/terms) and the [Community User Terms](http://jaycut.com/community-user-terms), and sets forth the terms and conditions relating to users’ privacy as defined below. Capitalized terms in this policy shall have the meaning attributed to them either in the JayCut [Terms of Use](http://jaycut.com/terms) or in the [Community User Terms](http://jaycut.com/community-user-terms), depending on the nature of your use.

    **1\. What is covered in this Privacy Policy**  
In this policy it is described how JayCut treats personal information that is collected and/or received, including information related to your past use of JayCut’s website, editor (regardless of if it is located on JayCut’s website or the website of a 3rd party) or other products or services supplied by JayCut. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

  This policy does not apply to any practices of companies that JayCut does not own or control, or to people that JayCut does not employ or manage.

    **2\. What information do we collect?**  
JayCut collects personal information in several cases, for example (but not limited to) when you register a JayCut account, when you use the JayCut Website, when you use JayCut’s video editing platform and other related technologies on the JayCut website and on the websites of 3rd parties who use JayCut’s API, when you visit JayCut pages or the pages of certain partners to JayCut, and when you enter promotions, contests, competitions and the like made available by JayCut. JayCut may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:  

  1. information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website or of the editing tool and other JayCut products even if these are located on 3rd party websites (including your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views);
  2. information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services (including name, company name, company website, website, product or service in which the video editor and other JayCut products will be used, billing address and other information required for customer identification and payment);
  3. informationthat you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us and using the JayCut website (including name, age, email, description, city and country of residence, picture and webpage);
  4. information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters (including name and email); and
  5. any other information that you choose to send to us.

**3\. Cookies**  
A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.

  JayCut may use both “session” cookies and “persistent” cookies on the JayCut website. JayCut may also use web beacons to access JayCut cookies inside and outside this website and in connection with JayCut products and services.

  JayCut use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers.  The information generated relating to JayCut’s website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information.  Google's privacy policy is available at: <http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html>.

  JayCut may also let other companies that provide payment service solutions or that show advertisements on some of JayCut’s pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one.

  Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, whilst some browsers allow you to reject just third party cookies.  For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector.  Blocking all cookies will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one.  

  **4\. Using your personal data**  
Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.

  JayCut may use your personal information to:  

  1. administer the website;
  2. improve your browsing experience by personalising the website;
  3. enable your use of the services available on the website;
  4. supply to you services purchased via the website;
  5. send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you;
  6. send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications;
  7. send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;
  8. send to you our newsletter and other marketing communications relating to our business which we think may be of interest to you by email;
  9. provide third parties with statistical information about our users – but this information will not be used to identify any individual user; and
  10. deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to JayCut’s website, products or services.

All JayCut’s website financial transactions are handled through JayCut’s payment services provider, Paypal. You should only provide your personal information to Paypal after reviewing the Paypal privacy policy (available at [www.paypal.com](http://www.paypal.com/ "www.paypal.com")). JayCut will share information with Paypal only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing payments you make via this website or the websites of JayCut resellers or affiliates.

    **5\. Disclosures**  
JayCut may disclose information about you to any of JayCut’s employees, officers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy.

  In addition, JayCut may disclose information about you:  

  1. to the extent required to do so by law;
  2. in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;
  3. in order to establish, exercise or defend JayCut’s legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk); and
  4. to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset which JayCut is (or is contemplating) selling.

Except as provided in this privacy policy, JayCut will not provide your information to third parties.

    **6\. International data transfers**  
Information that JayCut collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which JayCut operates in order to enable use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy. This also extends to countries in which JayCut or a 3rd party contracted by JayCut has data centers.

  Information which you provide may be transferred to countries (including the United States) which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the European Economic Areas (EEA).

  In addition, some personal information that you submit for publication on this website in relation to your account profile will be published on the internet and may be available, via the internet, around the world.

  You expressly agree to such transfers and availability of personal information.

    **7\. Security of your personal data**  
JayCut will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. This is done by having physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards.  
Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and JayCut cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.

  You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential. JayCut will never ask you for your password.

    **8\. Policy amendments**  
JayCut may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on this website.  You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes. 

  JayCut may also notify you of significant changes to this privacy policy by email.

    **9\. Your rights**  
You can edit your JayCut account information at any time by logging into your account.

  New categories of communications and notification might be added from time to time. You can opt out of receiving future communications from these new categories or you can unsubscribe and/or block future messages by following instructions contained in the received messages.

  You can delete your JayCut account at any time by following the instructions on the relevant section of this website. JayCut tries not to keep any information and user uploaded media in our records after your account has been deleted, but you acknowledge that it for technical and practical reasons may still persist for some time after account deletion.  

  **10\. Third party websites**  
The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.

    **11\. Contact**  
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us by email to [info@jaycut.com](mailto:info@jaycut.com) or by post to JayCut AB, Wallingatan 18 bv, 111 24 Stockholm, Sweden.
